<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>I am currently a M.S. candidate at UCLA studying mechanical engineering with a breadth in engineering design, as well as a smaller focus in mechanics and machine learning. My professional experiences include the medical device, product development, and aerospace industries.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 22:20:28 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 22:20:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to my portfolio site!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi there! My name is Dennis Shen and I am currently a M.S. candidate at UCLA studying mechanical engineering. This is my personal portfolio website, where I have chosen to highlight some of my previous work experiences and projects. Additionally, the contents of this website may change every so often, so feel free to check back when you want! The website is built by me using Jekyll and GitHub Pages, with the ‘Steve’ theme from Jekyll Themes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my free time, I have been working on a few side projects (including making an arcade style game controller for a game called Rhythm Doctor), taking care of my house plants, and learning to cook more yummy food! Feel free to look around and connect with me on LinkedIn or by email if you have any questions or comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A picture of my favorite spider plant!&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/spider.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;plants&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/intro.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/intro.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
